<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin, Author at CNN Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/author/admin/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:18:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Dominican Republic, Canada disagree over Haitian police aid office</title>
		<link>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/dominican-republic-canada-disagree-over-haitian-police-aid-office/</link>
					<comments>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/dominican-republic-canada-disagree-over-haitian-police-aid-office/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[International]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cnn.online.mills.edu/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are a California consumer, you have the right, at any time, to direct a business that sells your personal information to third parties to not sell your personal information. This right is referred to as the right to opt-out. You may exercise your right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/dominican-republic-canada-disagree-over-haitian-police-aid-office/">Dominican Republic, Canada disagree over Haitian police aid office</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are a California consumer, you have the right, at any time, to direct a business that sells your personal information to third parties to not sell your personal information. This right is referred to as the right to opt-out. You may exercise your right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information through Reuters.com by clicking here. You do not have to create an account to exercise this right.</p>



<p>Please note that opting-out may not mean you will stop seeing advertisements. Additionally, in the event you opt-out under CCPA, but do not opt out of interest-based advertising more generally, you may still receive advertisements tailored to your interests based upon your Personal Information. For more information about your rights as a California consumer and to learn more about our use of interest-based advertising and additional opt-out choices, please see our Privacy Statement.</p>



<p>When you visit our website, we store cookies on your browser to collect information. The information collected might relate to you, your preferences or your device, and is mostly used to make the site work as you expect it to and to provide a more personalized web experience. However, you can choose not to allow certain types of cookies, which may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer. Click on the different category headings to find out more and change our default settings according to your preference. You cannot opt-out of our First Party Strictly Necessary Cookies as they are deployed in order to ensure the proper functioning of our website (such as prompting the cookie banner and remembering your settings, to log into your account, to redirect you when you log out, etc.). For more information about the First and Third Party Cookies used please follow this link.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="manage-cookies-text">Manage Consent Preferences</h3>



<p>Always Active</p>



<p>Strictly Necessary Cookies</p>



<p id="ot-desc-id-1">These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. &nbsp; &nbsp;You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.</p>



<ul>
<li>Functional CookiesThese cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalisation. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages. &nbsp; &nbsp;If you do not allow these cookies then some or all of these services may not function properly.</li>
</ul>



<p>Always Active</p>



<p>Sale of Personal Data</p>



<p>Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information to third parties. These cookies collect information for analytics and to personalize your experience with targeted ads. You may exercise your right to opt out of the sale of personal information by using this toggle switch. If you opt out we will not be able to offer you personalised ads and will not hand over your personal information to any third parties. Additionally, you may contact our legal department for further clarification about your rights as a California consumer by using this Exercise My Rights link.</p>



<p>If you have enabled privacy controls on your browser (such as a plugin), we have to take that as a valid request to opt-out. Therefore we would not be able to track your activity through the web. This may affect our ability to personalize ads according to your preferences.</p>



<ul>
<li>Performance CookiesThese cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. &nbsp; &nbsp;All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.</li>
</ul>



<ul>
<li>Targeting CookiesThese cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. &nbsp; &nbsp;They do not store directly personal information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/dominican-republic-canada-disagree-over-haitian-police-aid-office/">Dominican Republic, Canada disagree over Haitian police aid office</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/dominican-republic-canada-disagree-over-haitian-police-aid-office/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mirabai Chanu to train in USA ahead of Asian Games 2023</title>
		<link>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/mirabai-chanu-to-train-in-usa-ahead-of-asian-games-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/mirabai-chanu-to-train-in-usa-ahead-of-asian-games-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cnn.online.mills.edu/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mirabai Chanu, the silver medallist at the Tokyo 2020 Olympics, will undergo training in the United States after her proposal to train abroad was approved by the Mission Olympic Cell (MOC) of the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports of India. The athlete has already flown out of the country and is on her way</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/mirabai-chanu-to-train-in-usa-ahead-of-asian-games-2023/">Mirabai Chanu to train in USA ahead of Asian Games 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Mirabai Chanu, the silver medallist at the Tokyo 2020 Olympics, will undergo training in the United States after her proposal to train abroad was approved by the Mission Olympic Cell (MOC) of the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports of India.</p>



<p>The athlete has already flown out of the country and is on her way to St. Louis where she will train at&nbsp;Dr Aron Horschig&#8217;s SQUAT University. She will focus on strength training as part of her preparations for the upcoming Asian Games 2023 which are scheduled to take place in Hangzhou, China, from September 23 to October 8.</p>



<p>The official Twitter handle of the Sports Authority of India (SAI) announced the development and wrote: &#8220;MOC approves a 65 days long training camp for CWG Medalists @mirabai_chanu &amp; @BindyaraniS at St. Louis, <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png" alt="🇺🇸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> with Dr. Aaron Horschig. #TOPSchemeAthletes will be training at @SquatUniversity to prepare for the all important #AsianGames2022.&#8221;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Chanu made her comeback to competitive action in May after completing a five-month rehabilitation program following her hip surgery in December last year. In her first competition of the season, the 28-year-old weightlifter secured a sixth-place finish at the Asian Weightlifting Championships 2023 held in Jinju, South Korea.</p>



<p>Chanu will be accompanied by Indian chief coach Vijay Sharma and physiotherapist Tesneem Zayyad during the 65-day trip to the United States</p>



<p>The Mission Olympic Cell also approved the training proposal of Bindyarani Devi, a silver medallist at the Commonwealth Games 2022.</p>



<p>Bindyarani Devi, 24 years old, secured the silver medal in the women&#8217;s 55kg category at the Asian Weightlifting Championships 2023 held in South Korea earlier in May. She will also train in St. Louis, along with Chanu in their pursuit of excellence in the forthcoming Asian Games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/mirabai-chanu-to-train-in-usa-ahead-of-asian-games-2023/">Mirabai Chanu to train in USA ahead of Asian Games 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/mirabai-chanu-to-train-in-usa-ahead-of-asian-games-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Suns Cam Johnson, Mikal Bridges join Team USA for FIBA World Cup</title>
		<link>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/former-suns-cam-johnson-mikal-bridges-join-team-usa-for-fiba-world-cup/</link>
					<comments>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/former-suns-cam-johnson-mikal-bridges-join-team-usa-for-fiba-world-cup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cnn.online.mills.edu/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Athletics&#8217; potential move to Las Vegas is far from a done deal, but the team took a massive leap this week when Senate Bill 1 was signed into law by Nevada Gov. Joe Lombardo. Still, former Miami Marlins president David Samson has a hard time believing the possible relocation will come to fruition. &#8220;I want to</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/former-suns-cam-johnson-mikal-bridges-join-team-usa-for-fiba-world-cup/">Former Suns Cam Johnson, Mikal Bridges join Team USA for FIBA World Cup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Athletics&#8217; potential move to Las Vegas is far from a done deal, but the team took a massive leap this week when Senate Bill 1 was signed into law by Nevada Gov. Joe Lombardo.</p>



<p>Still, former Miami Marlins president David Samson has a hard time believing the possible relocation will come to fruition.</p>



<p>&#8220;I want to give you one thing to think about, and we can make this two segments or zero segments. There is no ballpark that can fit on nine acres of land that has a retractable roof. That&#8217;s the start and the end of this discussion,&#8221; Samson said on &#8220;The Dan Lebatard Show,&#8221; which was published Thursday morning. &#8220;But if you want to keep going, there&#8217;s no approval by baseball to relocate, there&#8217;s no financial plan of what the A&#8217;s would be doing in Las Vegas for the owners to vote on, there&#8217;s no TV deal, there&#8217;s no set private financing for [A&#8217;s owner] John Fisher for his portion of a stadium in Las Vegas.</p>



<p>&#8220;All that happened is the framework of the public part of the public-private partnership for a stadium in Vegas. That&#8217;s all this special session was. That&#8217;s all the public money is. But it&#8217;s step one of 50. And last night, the A&#8217;s released a statement that I went into detail on &#8216;Nothing Personal&#8217; today, but I&#8217;ll sum it up now, a statement that merely said, &#8216;When the governor signs this into law, that will be a good next step.&#8217; And that&#8217;s all that is.&#8221;</p>



<p>Samson was president of the Marlins from 2002 until 2017. Miami won the World Series in 2003, but it faced a major challenge as far as long-term stability in a baseball-only stadium with South Florida weather the biggest concern for the team.</p>



<p>The first two owners of the Marlins, Wayne Huizenga and John Henry, couldn&#8217;t seal the deal on a new facility, but Samson led a negotiating team that worked for more than six years to finalize a partnership to build a new retractable roof, air-conditioned ballpark in Miami.</p>



<p>Samson knows better than anyone how difficult it is to fight for a new stadium, and he was very critical of the way Fisher has gone about things.</p>



<p>&#8220;The boycott is not relevant, the fact that the team stinks is not relevant, what is relevant is that owners want to get the A&#8217;s out of the revenue-sharing receiver position,&#8221; Samson continued. &#8220;What&#8217;s also relevant is that the owners want expansion money so they can pay off the debt that they incurred during COVID, that they&#8217;ve incurred over time because salaries are too high and so they&#8217;ve got to get Oakland and Tampa [Bay Rays] taken care of before expansion. But it&#8217;s not done yet.&#8221;</p>



<p>The Howard Terminal project was the A&#8217;s last hope to stay in Oakland. The team&#8217;s exclusive negotiation agreement with the port of Oakland for the multibillion-dollar waterfront site expired on May 12.</p>



<p>Thereafter, Fisher and the A&#8217;s shifted their focus to Southern Nevada. But Samson doesn&#8217;t believe the door fully has closed on Howard Terminal.</p>



<p>&#8220;I think it could still be built at the Howard Terminal. I think they were closer to a deal in Oakland than they even are in Vegas,&#8221; he said. &#8220;The problem is that Josh Fisher has screwed it up so badly that it&#8217;s made our effort &#8212; Wayne Huizenga and John Henry&#8217;s in Florida &#8212; it&#8217;s made our effort look amazing because of everything he&#8217;s done wrong along the way from both a [public relations] standpoint and just a practical standpoint of how to get a deal done.</p>



<p>&#8220;I think MLB needs Vegas as an expansion candidate and to waste them as a relocation is a real disservice to maximizing your expansion fee, and that&#8217;s what owners are concerned about right now. That&#8217;s why there wasn&#8217;t a vote with the owners meetings that are going on in New York right now because there&#8217;s nothing to vote on yet. Do I think eventually the A&#8217;s move to Vegas? I&#8217;m still a no on that. And I&#8217;ll be the last to hold out, and I&#8217;ll come on the show to admit that I was wrong, but there&#8217;s nothing that tells me that a deal to Vegas is anywhere near complete.&#8221;</p>



<p>Before LoanDepot Park was built, the Marlins were in headlines to potentially relocate to other cities like San Antonio, Vegas and Portland. Samson said there was no truth to that.</p>



<p>While things certainly appear different for the A&#8217;s as they continue to push for their brand-new ballpark, Samson is pretty confident in how it will all play out.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/former-suns-cam-johnson-mikal-bridges-join-team-usa-for-fiba-world-cup/">Former Suns Cam Johnson, Mikal Bridges join Team USA for FIBA World Cup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/former-suns-cam-johnson-mikal-bridges-join-team-usa-for-fiba-world-cup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Taylor Swift makes history as she takes over the entire US top 10</title>
		<link>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/taylor-swift-makes-history-as-she-takes-over-the-entire-us-top-10/</link>
					<comments>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/taylor-swift-makes-history-as-she-takes-over-the-entire-us-top-10/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cnn.online.mills.edu/?p=9</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Taylor Swift has become the first artist in history to claim every slot in the top 10 of the US singles chart. She overtakes Drake, who held the previous record of nine top 10 singles in September 2021. Before him, the Beatles scored eight top 10s in 1964. Swift&#8217;s chart domination is thanks to her</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/taylor-swift-makes-history-as-she-takes-over-the-entire-us-top-10/">Taylor Swift makes history as she takes over the entire US top 10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Taylor Swift has become the first artist in history to claim every slot in the top 10 of the US singles chart.</strong></p>



<p>She overtakes Drake, who held the previous record of nine top 10 singles in September 2021. Before him, the Beatles scored eight top 10s in 1964.</p>



<p>Swift&#8217;s chart domination is thanks to her latest album, Midnights, which has become 2022&#8217;s fastest-selling release.</p>



<p>&#8220;10 out of 10 of the Hot 100??? On my 10th album??? I AM IN SHAMBLES,&#8221; tweeted the pop star.</p>



<p>The 32-year-old claims the number one spot with the single Anti-Hero, whose chorus, &#8220;<em>It&#8217;s me. Hi! I&#8217;m the problem, it&#8217;s me</em>,&#8221; has quickly become a Tik Tok trend.</p>



<p>The rest of the top 10 includes album tracks like Lavender Haze, Maroon, Snow On The Beach, Bejewelled and Karma.</p>



<p>All 13 of the songs on Midnights&#8217; standard edition make the top 15, interrupted only by Sam Smith&#8217;s Unholy at 11 and Steve Lacy&#8217;s Bad Habits at 12.</p>



<p>The seven bonus tracks from Midnights&#8217; deluxe &#8220;3am edition&#8221; appear between numbers 20 and 45.</p>



<p>Swift took fans by surprise when she announced the new album in the closing moments of the 2022 MTV VMAs in New Jersey in August.</p>



<p>She has described the record as the story of &#8220;13 sleepless nights scattered throughout my life&#8221; and &#8220;a journey through terrors and sweet dreams&#8221;.</p>



<p>It sees the star return to the pop palette of her pre-pandemic albums, after the homespun indie-folk of Evermore and Folklore, both released in 2020.</p>



<p>But the subdued sounds of those records persists, and her late-night tales are painted in more muted tones than hits like Shake It Off and Lover.</p>



<p>Part of its success is due to a clever marketing campaign, which saw the album released in multiple collectible formats &#8211; including four vinyl editions which combine to make a clock.</p>



<p>But Billboard reported that Swift&#8217;s Top 10 takeover would have been achieved by streams alone, before sales and radio play were counted.</p>



<p>This YouTube post cannot be displayed in your browser. Please enable Javascript or try a different browser.View original content on YouTube</p>



<p>The BBC is not responsible for the content of external sites. YouTube content may contain adverts.</p>



<p>Allow YouTube content?</p>



<p>This article contains content provided by Google YouTube. We ask for your permission before anything is loaded, as they may be using cookies and other technologies. You may want to read Google’s cookie policy, external and privacy policy, external before accepting. To view this content choose <strong>‘accept and continue’</strong>.</p>



<p>The BBC is not responsible for the content of external sites. YouTube content may contain adverts.</p>



<p>Midnights debuted at number one in the US album chart, selling 1.4 million copies &#8211; with more than one million of those on CD and vinyl, an almost unheard of figure in the streaming era.</p>



<p>The album similarly tops the UK chart with sales of 204,000, making it the first album to crack the 200,000 sales barrier since Adele&#8217;s 30 just under a year ago.</p>



<p>Surprisingly, that figure represents the biggest first-week sales of Swift&#8217;s UK chart career. Her previous best was for the album 1989, which shifted 90,300 copies in 2014.</p>



<p>However, she cannot replicate her domination of the US singles countdown &#8211; due to a UK chart rule that only allows three songs by one artist to appear in the Top 100 at the same time.</p>



<p>Without that restriction, Swift would have had eight of this week&#8217;s top 10 singles. Instead, she has to content herself with being number one (Anti-Hero), three (Lavender Haze) and four (Snow On The Beach).</p>



<p>Last week&#8217;s number one, Sam Smith&#8217;s Unholy, clings on at number two, denying Swift a clean sweep at the top of the charts.</p>



<p>Billboard magazine said Swift&#8217;s latest album had helped her break several records.</p>



<p>She now boasts the most top 10 hits among women in the chart&#8217;s history, with her total of 40 surpassing Madonna&#8217;s 38. Amongst all acts, she trails only Drake, who has 59 top 10s.</p>



<p>Midnights is also the first album in history to spawn 10 top 10 singles.</p>



<p>Swift also broke records for the most streams of a single album in one day on Spotify, Apple and Amazon Music.</p>



<p>In the UK, Midnights sold 62,000 copies on vinyl alone &#8211; the highest weekly sale for any vinyl album in the 21st century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/taylor-swift-makes-history-as-she-takes-over-the-entire-us-top-10/">Taylor Swift makes history as she takes over the entire US top 10</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/taylor-swift-makes-history-as-she-takes-over-the-entire-us-top-10/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Karisma Kapoors throwback beach snap gets hilarious response from Kareena</title>
		<link>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/karisma-kapoors-throwback-beach-snap-gets-hilarious-response-from-kareena/</link>
					<comments>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/karisma-kapoors-throwback-beach-snap-gets-hilarious-response-from-kareena/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cnn.online.mills.edu/?p=6</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kareena Kapoor’s relationship with her sister Karisma is pure goals. The Laal Singh Chaddha star never fails to drop adorable photos with Karisma. But, this time it was Karisma Kapoor who grabbed attention for her throwback photo with Bebo. Taken from their trip to Maldives last year, Karisma’s photo is proof of her sweet bond</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/karisma-kapoors-throwback-beach-snap-gets-hilarious-response-from-kareena/">Karisma Kapoors throwback beach snap gets hilarious response from Kareena</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Kareena Kapoor’s relationship with her sister Karisma is pure goals. The Laal Singh Chaddha star never fails to drop adorable photos with Karisma. But, this time it was Karisma Kapoor who grabbed attention for her throwback photo with Bebo. Taken from their trip to Maldives last year, Karisma’s photo is proof of her sweet bond with Kareena. In case you missed it, the banter between the siblings is the one thing you must see on social media today.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Karisma Kapoor&#8217;s post &nbsp;</h2>



<p>It all started when Karisma Kapoor dropped a picture of her holiday with Kareena. The picture captures Karisma striking a pose while Kareena relaxes on a hammock, busy on her phone. Karisma wore a blue and black bikini top and oversized sunglasses, showcasing her natural beauty with a no-makeup look. The Hero No 1 star playfully captioned the image, &#8220;Pouting while the sister is Scrolling #rolereversal #throwback #sistersquad.&#8221;</p>



<p>Not one to be outdone, Kareena Kapoor responded to Karisma&#8217;s post on her Instagram Stories. She shared the photo and captioned it as, &#8220;Learning to pout, I see,&#8221; accompanied by starry-eyed and heart-eyed emojis. &nbsp;Adorable, right?</p>



<p>Appreciating her sister&#8217;s response, Karisma Kapoor re-shared Kareena&#8217;s post on her own Instagram Stories She wrote, &#8220;Learning from the best,&#8221; along with hugging face and red heart emojis.</p>



<p>The photo is Karisma Kapoor and Kareena Kapoor&#8217;s Maldives vacation with their children &#8211; Taimur Ali Khan, Jeh Ali Khan, Samaira Kapoor, and Kiaan Raj Kapoor.</p>



<p>Karisma and Kareena Kapoor’s upcoming projects<br>Currently, Kareena Kapoor Khan is occupied with filming her upcoming project, titled The Crew. The movie features Tabu and Kriti Sanon. The Crew is produced by Rhea Kapoor. Additionally, Kareena has Sujoy Ghosh’s The Devotion Of Suspect X. It also stars Vijay Varma and Jaideep Ahlawat. The Jab We Met star also has an untitled project helmed by Hansal Mehta in her kitty.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Karisma Kapoor is gearing up for her return to the entertainment industry with the series Brown. She is also set to appear in Homi Adajania&#8217;s Murder Mubarak, alongside Sara Ali Khan, Sanjay Kapoor, and Vijay Varma.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu/karisma-kapoors-throwback-beach-snap-gets-hilarious-response-from-kareena/">Karisma Kapoors throwback beach snap gets hilarious response from Kareena</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cnn.online.mills.edu">CNN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cnn.online.mills.edu/karisma-kapoors-throwback-beach-snap-gets-hilarious-response-from-kareena/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
